Good artists create. Great artists steal.
Lying and Stealing is a crime, comedy, drama film directed by Matt Aselton.
Hoping to leave his criminal lifestyle behind him, a successful art thief teams up with
a sexy con woman to pull off the ultimate heist and set himself free.
Ivan, played by Theo James.
Elyse, played by Emily Ratajkowski.
Dimitri, played by Fred Melamed.
Pool Man, played by Aris Alvarado.
Mary, played by Fernanda Andrade.
Aaron, played by Tim Bader.
Lying and Stealing is a 2019 American crime drama film, directed by Matt
Aselton from a screenplay by Aselton and Adam Nagata.
It stars Theo James, Emily Ratajkowski, Fred Melamed,
Ebon Moss-Bachrach, Isiah Whitlock Jr.
and Evan Handler.
It was released on July 12, 2019, by Vertical Entertainment.
The film explores themes of fbi, thief, stealing, art thief, agent.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.